Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory7 Mss.B.B61.inventory07
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents K
  - Kallen, Horace M. (Box 49)
    - H.M. Kallen -- to A.H. Hirsch, 1934 Dec. 26; 2p.
    - H.M. Kallen -- to A.H. Hirsch, 1934 Dec. 26; 2p.
    - (With Hirsch, A.H. to Kallen, H.M., Jan. 9, 1935)
    - H.M. Kallen -- from A.H. Hirsch, 1935 Jan. 9
  - Kallman, Franz J. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 4p.
    - (Enc. with Kallman, Franz Oct. 26, 1936), 1936 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Parsons, F.W. Dec. 8,1936, 1936 Dec. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec.; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Committee on Anthropology Oct. 17, 1938., 1938 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 6; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July
    - Curriculum Vitae, 1935 Dec; 4p.
    - See: Greutzfeld, 1935 Oct. 30
    - Bonhoeffer, 1935 Oct. 30
    - Birnbaum, 1935 Oct. 31
    - Pansa, 1935 Oct. 22
    - Probst, 1935 Dec. 23
    - Ruedin, 1935 May 30
    - Fels, M., 1927 Jan. 12
    - Koebisch, 1921 Nov. 3
    - Petersen-Borsel, 1920 Dec. 16
    - (Enc. with Kallmann, Franz with Parsons, F.W., Oct. 26, 1936 Dec. 8, 1936
  - Kamaiko, Jack (Box 49)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; telegram
  - Kambulain, A.F. (Box 49)
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 22
  - Kameneva, O.D. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1927 June 20; 1p.
  - Kandel, J.L. (Box 49)
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - (Enc: Kandel, D.L. to Thomas, W.K., Sept. 24, 1934)
    - See Boas, F. open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938.
    - J.L. Kandel -- to W.K. Thomas, 1935 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Kandel, J.L., Jan. 22, 1935)
  - Kane, F.F. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 26; 1p.
  - Kane, H.P. (Box 49)
    - To Boas, 1893 Apr. 2; 1p.
  - Kane, Harnett T. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 1; 1p.
  - Kantor, John L. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1918 Sept. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 27; 1p.
  - Kantrowitz, Hugo (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p.
  - Kapelsohn, Sol D. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 17; 1p.
  - Kaplan, Anna S. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 24; 1p.
  - Kaplan, H.E. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 27; 1p.
  - Kaplan, I. (Box 49)
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 12; 2p.
  - Kappers, Ariens (Box 49)
    General note
    1 person
    - From Boas, 1936 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 4; 4p.
  - Kappers, C.U.A. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 14; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept. 13; 3p.
  - Kardiner, Abram (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 24; 1p.
  - Karge, G. (Box 49)
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 8; 4p.
  - Karl-Franzens University (Box 49)
    - Enc. with letter to Boas, F. to Voorhis, Harold O., Nov. 3, 1932.
  - Karlgren, B. (Box 49)
    - B. Karlgren -- to J. Schrijnen, 1928 Feb. 10; 2p.
    - (Enc. in Schrijnen, J., Oct. 25, 1928)
  - Karmer, Emil (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p.
  - Karnit, Irene T. (Box 49)
    - See Boas, F. (Open letter), June 20, 1940.
  - Karpf, Maurice J. (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 9; 2p.
    - (Enc: Training School for Jewish Social Work....Post war problems of the Jews), 1926 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - M.J. Karpf -- from Frederick W. Parsons, 1935 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - (Enc. with letter from Malzberg, Benjamin to Boas, F.), dated Jan. 31, 1935
  - Kartographisches Institut (Box 49)
    - From Boas, 1923 Sept. 4; 1p.
    - See Mü???, Oct. 8, 1926 and Oct. 12, 1926
    - From Boas, 1927 Jan. 22; 1p.
  - Kaser, Max (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 28; 1p.
  - Kasner, Edward (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas
    - See Boas, F. to Kasner, E. margin., Nov. 11, 1942-
  - Kast, Ludwig (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 16; 1p.
  - Kast, M. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 22; 2p.
  - Kate, Herman ten (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 June 5
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 11; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 13; postca.
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 July 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - H. ten Kate -- to Goddard, 1917 May 14
  - Katz, Helen M. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 24; 2p.
  - Katz, Sidney (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 3; 1p.
  - Katzenstein, S. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p.
  - Kaufman, George S. (Box 50)
    - See Brooks, V.W., Nov. 22, 1938.
  - Kaufmann, E.I. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 16; telegram
    - To Boas, 1935 June 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 6; 1p.
    - (Enc: Warner, H.M. to Kaufmann, E.I. June 4, 1935), 1935 June 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 7; 1p.
    - E.I. Kaufmann -- from H.M. Warner, 1935 June 4
    - (Enc. with Kaufmann, E.I., June 6, 1935)
  - Kaufmann, M. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 18; 1p.
  - M. Kaufmann to Wohlauer?, 1926 Mar. 25; 1p. (Box 50)
  - Kautzenbach, George (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 9; 2p.
  - Kaye, S. Aaron (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1926 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 15; 1p.
  - Kayser, Carl F. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Klenze, C. v. Nov. 24, 1920., 1920 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - C.F. Kayser -- from Emergency society for German and Austrian science and art, 1920 Dec. 31
    - (See Emergency society...art (to Speyer,J., Dec. 31, 1920)
  - Kayser, Eva A. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; bill
  - Kazanjian, L. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 30; 1p.
  - Kearny, J.L. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 11
    - To Boas, 1908 May 8
  - Keates (Box 50)
    - From P.E. Goddard, 1927 Apr. 25
  - Keck, E.J. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1894 June 23
  - Keehn, Harriet (Box 50)
    - From Emergency society in aid of European science and art, 1920 Nov. 1
    - See Emergency society in aid of European science and art to Keehn, H., Nov. 27, 1920.
  - Keeler, M. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 22; 6p.
  - Keely, Paul (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 23; 1p.
  - Keen, J.H. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 8; 1p.
  - Keen, W.W. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 9; 1p.
  - Kefauver, Grayson N. (Box 50)
    - G.N. Kefauver -- to C.R. Miller, 1939 July 7; 1p.
  - Keibel, Franz (Box 50)
    - F. Keibel -- to Greenman, 1920 Nov. 22
  - Keissler, Karl (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1927 May 24; 1p.
  - Keith, S. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p.
  - Kelijuran, E.R. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 26; 4p
  - Keller, A.G. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 15
  - Keller, Eleanor (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 26
  - Keller, Helen (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 12; 1p.
  - Keller, I. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1891 end; 2p.
  - Keller, J. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 23
  - Kelley, Nicholas (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 14; 1p.
  - Kelley, T.R. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - (Enc: Papers for Rainbow Bridge-Monumeny Valley Expedition), 1935 Apr. 8; 2p.
  - Kellogg, Paul U. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - See Niebuhr, Reinhold, Apr. 22, 1940
  - Kellogg, Vernon (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - (Attached: Kellogg, V. to Bryan, R.W. Dec. 18, 1930), 1931 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 3; 1p.
      (Enc: National research council. Executive Board. Science advisory committee. Report.)
    - V. Kellogg -- to R.W. Bryan, 1930 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - (Attached to Boas, F. to Kellogg, V., Jan. 13, 1931)
    - V. Kellogg -- from W.C. Mitchell, 1928 Mar. 12
    - (Enc. with Mitchell, W.C., Mar. 12, 1928)
    - V. Kellogg -- to National research council Executive Board, 1931 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 28; 1p.
  - Kelly, (Thomas A. Edison Co.) (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 21; 1p.
  - Kelly, A.K. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 30; 2p.
  - Kelly, A.R. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 13; 1p.
  - Kelly, Henry A. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 28; 1p.
  - Kelly, J.H. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 19; 1p.
  - Kelsey, C. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 27; 1p.
  - Kelsey, Francis W. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 16; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 16; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1909 May 26
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 3
    - F.W. Kelsey -- to Miss Andrews, 1911 Feb. 2
    - F.W. Kelsey -- from N.S. Spencer, 1911 Feb. 16
    - F.W. Kelsey -- from N.S. Spencer, 1911 Feb. 20
    - F.W. Kelsey -- from N.S. Spencer, 1911 Feb. 24
    - F.W. Kelsey -- from N.S. Spencer, 1911 Feb. 27
    - F.W. Kelsey -- to N.S. Spencer, 1911 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - F.W. Kelsey -- to N.S. Spencer, 1911 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - F.W. Kelsey -- to N.S. Spencer, 1911 Mar. 2; 1p.
  - Keltie (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1887 Sept. 13
  - Kemble, C.S. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 9; postcard
  - Kemenov, V. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 6; 1p.
  - Kemp, J.F. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 10; 3p.
  - Kendall, C.N. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 23; 2p.
  - Keniston, Hayward (Box 50)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Kennaday, P. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 June 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1917 June 20
  - Kennaday, R.T. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 27
  - Kennard, E.A. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 24; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 14; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1938 July 3; 1p.
  - Kennard, Lawaune E. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec.
  - Kennedy, R.T. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 15; 1p.
  - Kennelly, A.E. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 7; 2p.
  - Kent, Frances (Mrs. Rockwell) (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - (Enc: Browder, Earl to Kent, Rockwell, Feb. 20, 1939)
  - Kent, Henry W. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 31; 1p.
  - Kent, Rockwell -- follows Roland G. (Box 50)
  - Kent, Roland G. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - (On copy: Sapir, E. Feb. 18, 1929), 1929 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 15; postal
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 19; postal
    - To Boas, 1937 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - (Enc: Linguistic Society of America. Regulations adopted, May 1, 1937.)
    - R.G. Kent -- to G.M. Bolling, 1938 May 13; 1p.
    - R.G. Kent -- to R.W. Bryan, 1930 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - R.G. Kent -- to Group for Amer. Indian linquistics Administrative committee, 1938 May 20; 1p.
    - R.G. Kent -- from W.G. Leland, 1928 Apr. 18
    - (Enc. originally with Leland, W.G. to Boas, F. & Kent, R.G., Apr. 18, 1928)
    - R.G. Kent -- to Linguistic Society of Amer. Executive Comm., 1925 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - (Enc: Minutes of the organization meeting, signed by T. Michelson. Includes constitution.), 1925 Jan. 12
    - R.G. Kent -- to Linguistic Society of Amer. Executive Comm., 1925 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - R.G. Kent -- to Linguistic Society of Amer. Executive Comm., 1925 Sept. 28; 2p.
    - (Enc: Circulars for complimentary copies and offers for exchanges.), 1925 Nov. 30; 6p.
    - R.G. Kent -- to Linguistic Society of Amer. Executive Comm., 1937 May 8; 1p.
    - R.G. Kent -- from E.H. Sturtevant, 1927 Apr. 15
    - R.G. Kent -- to S.W.J. Teeuwen, 1929 Apr. 17; 1p.
  - Kent, Rockwell (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - R. Kent -- from Earl Browder, 1939 Feb. 20
    - (Enc. with Kent, Frances, Feb. 23, 1939)
  - Kenyon, D. (Box 50)
    - See Field, F., Sept. 20, 1935
  - Kepler, M.S. (Box 50)
    - To Boas, 1906 May 16; 1p.
  - Kepler, N.B. (Box 50)
    - N.B. Kepler -- to K.G. Buenz, 1906 Mar. 16; 1p.
  - Keppel, Frederick P. (Box 50)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 15; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Aug. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Sept. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 1; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - (Enc: List of mms. on Indian languages on hand.), 1929 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas (no. 1), 1930 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas (no. 2), 1930 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 9; 11p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 June 10; 2p.
    - (Enc: Report), 1940 June 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 June 17
    - To Boas, 1905 June 21
    - To Boas, 1905 July 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1906 May 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1909 July 1
    - To Boas, 1909 July 6
    - To Boas, 1909 July 6
    - To Boas, 1909 July 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 20
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 May 28
    - To Boas, 1910 June 30
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 15
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - F.P. Keppel -- to H.R. Bryan, 1933 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - F.P. Keppel -- from W.M. Brittain, 1906 Aug. 17
    - F.P. Keppel -- from FitzRoy Carrington, 1908 Oct. 26
    - F.P. Keppel -- from F.D. Chester, 1906 Aug. 14